Okay, now let's go on and take a look at Amazon Augmented AI.
So you need to know about this service at a high level, so let me just give you an overview.
So Amazon Augmented AI or Amazon A21 is a service that makes it easy to build the workflow
required for human review of machine learning predictions.
Now you can use human reviewers to step in when the model is unable to make a high
confidence prediction or to audit its predictions on an ongoing basis.
So now let me try and explain this through an example.
So now let's say our model is trying to predict whether the image that is being shown
is a cat or not.
Now let's just assume that we showed the first image and it is able to predict that
the image is a cat with 90% confidence.
So that's good.
Now let's say we showed another image and it is able to predict that it is not a cat but
with only 20% confidence level.
So then what we can do is we can create a workflow where we say that if the model is able
to predict an image with a high confidence level, then we are good.
But if it is not able to predict the image with a high confidence level, then that image
can go to a human or a person to review the prediction of the model.
So that is the key use case scenario for Amazon Augmented AI.
So it provides built-in human review workflow for common machine learning use case.
And I think we just discussed that.
So now let's take a real world use case on how it can be used.
So it can be used in the insurance industry for insurance claims intake forms and prescriptions.
So we can use Amazon text rack and implement human review of newest or sensitive data using
Amazon AI 21.
Then it can also be used for content moderation with Amazon Herak Commission.
So you can see a screenshot from Amazon Augmented AI and this should be shown to a human
reviewer.
So on the left side you have instructions on how you need to execute the task.
So once the human reviewer looks at the instruction, then you can have Amazon text rack extract
the data from a handwritten note into this form.
And then the human reviewer can mark the correctness of the data that has been imported
on this side.
Okay.
So that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture.
Thank you.